You
is it the dragon no luster grizzlies at two o'clock it's a whole pack they're kicking up the snow
how many eight no ten they know we're here and they're headed straight for us get ready
run out guys quagmire get down here we need you yes sir quagmire yep
charge
run out
yeah
you
Oh
Hey! It's the Red Dragon! Look out!
That's where the bears were running from!
Hey Quagmire, what the hell is this?
You better not have been slacking off!
I couldn't see it through that cloud of snow!
Damn it! Retreat! Now!
We'll conjure a smokescreen! Everyone split up!
Up.
Renden.
He got it!
Nice going.
You really are something special, Quagmire, you know that?
You weren't kidding about traveling the Demon Continent, huh?
Yeah, for real. I can't believe you actually beat that thing.
Well, it was pretty weak already.
Say, Quagmire, don't you think it's about damn time you joined our party for real?
You fit right in, and I know you don't mind our company too terribly.
Yeah, but once I make a name for myself out here, I'll have to move on again.
Sorry, but I still need to find my mother.
Thank you for protecting me out there today.
And then it appeared...
A giant red dragon!
But when it seemed as though all hope was lost,
he ensnared the great beast inside his namesake, a Quagmire,
and dropped a massive boulder on the struggling worm!
Tell a different one!
That's not very nice.
The hero of the story is sitting right here.
I finally found you, Quagmire Rudeus.
Uh...
Shit.
We're sitting right there.
Yes, ma'am.
You've tracked me down at last.
I have no idea who this lady is.
Yeah, you stick out like a sore thumb, just like she said you would.
I haven't been trying to hide.
Yes, well, I assumed you would be further out east.
What is this?
Love at first sight?
Or is she just after my body?
I have gotten manlier lately.
Plenty of muscle these days, etc.
I'm still a growing boy after all.
What's wrong?
Oh, nothing.
Nothing at all.
Who knew Quagmire had a woman?
Hmm.
My name is Alina Lise Dragon Road.
You may know this, but in case you don't,
I used to be in the same adventuring party as your father, Paul.
Oh, yeah?
Yes, indeed.
I'm also a friend of Roxy's.
Really?
You know my master?
Where is she these days?
That can wait.
Let's talk about you.
I heard you brought down a red worm all by yourself.
Yes, although it was half dead already.
I can see why Roxy boasts about you.
Does she really?
That's very flattering to hear, if a little embarrassed.
And you're touching me.
You don't mind, do you?
My, how strong you are.
Sorry, I'm kind of confused.
Do you have a thing for me by any chance?
Oh, yes.
You're so muscular.
Exactly my type.
You're a real man.
I had expected you would be more of a child still.
Okay.
Well, you're quite lovely yourself, Miss Selina Lise.
Ha!
Her teasing won't fluster me.
I'm not some virgin.
Whoa, wait.
She's putting out some serious vibes here.
Uh, you know what?
Okay, let's do this thing.
Oh, my goodness.
However, did you come by this pendant?
It's rough, but it's charming.
Oh, that was a gift from a friend.
A friend?
Were they elvish?
Huh?
Uh, yeah.
She is.
Uh, why do you ask?
No, there goes my shot.
No real reason.
Just curious.
Here, look at this.
We match.
I guess we do.
But I forget myself.
Do excuse the come on.
I wish you wouldn't tease me like that.
Oh, dear boy.
If there's one thing I never do, it's tease.
But I have no intention of becoming Paul's daughter-in-law by any means.
And I would prefer to remain friends with Roxy.
So, I take it you have some business here with me, then?
Yes.
I've come to bring you a bit of good news.
Have you now?
That day, I learned where Zenith was.
The labyrinth city of Rapa on the Begarit continent, far to the south.
The other side of the world.
Traveling there on foot from the northern territories could take a year, maybe more.
Besides, winter is coming.
I'll have to stay put for the time being, but I shouldn't have anything to worry about.
According to Alina Lee, Zenith is having a grand old time going dungeon diving.
And...
Don't fall over yourself to leave just yet.
We met Roxy while searching for your family and only split up once we found where Zenith was.
She and the others should have joined up with Paul in Militian by now and made their way down to Begarit to get her.
So you can relax, okay?
Wait, go back.
My master has been part of the search party all this time?
Paul doesn't inspire much confidence, but if Roxy's there, good.
Oh, Ridaeus.
Welcome back.
Morning, Alina Lee.
See, you're active, bright and early.
Active?
I...
Sure, I don't know what you mean by that.
It is pretty cold today, though, so try not to catch a chill.
Over the past week, I've learned that Alina Lee is slutty as hell, like damn.
She's got a different man in her room almost every day.
Sometimes two.
Or three.
The woman is a total man-eater.
Not that I'm judging her for it, of course.
I'd love to participate myself, but that's just not gonna happen.
Because for two years now, I've been suffering from a certain sickness.
The sickness of both body and mind.
In short, it's E.D.
And I've given up.
At a certain point, I realize no one can help me fix this.
And I don't like anyone enough to keep trying.
If all my attempts at romance are gonna end in betrayal,
I'd rather just admire from afar.
I swear I'm not crying.
Hey, this isn't what it looks like, Quagmire.
I had no intention of putting my hands on your woman.
Relax, soul.
It's all right.
Alina Lee isn't and has never been my woman.
Besides, you know I'm not exactly in working order.
Oh, yeah, right, I forgot.
Sorry about that, didn't mean to go rubbing salt in the wound there or anything.
I know, you're fine.
But it was good?
You had fun, right?
Oh, yeah.
She was amazing.
Well, you heard the man Alina Lee's rave reviews.
I know, it's what I do.
I'm proud to say I've never had a man who's left unsatisfied.
Really?
Good for them.
A few of the other guys in Soul's party have said the same to me already, but I'm not entirely sure they think of her as a team effort.
Just do me a favor.
Anything.
You're obviously free to help yourself to whomever, but deal with the aftermath on your own.
Oh, naturally.
Sorry.
What are you talking about?
Nothing.
Don't you worry.
Now why don't we get something to eat?
She's shameless.
But she crossed the Demon Continent with Roxy and then made her way here alone, all for Paul's sake.
So, she's gotta be a hell of a warrior.
With Roxy.
That'd be nice.
Damn you two, can't a guy eat in peace?
Super not jealous or anything, but how does this woman keep a harem of dudes around her and still avoid drama?
I mean, as long as the fallout doesn't hit me, whatever, but...
Here you are.
The money I promised you.
Thank you, m'lady.
You know, I feel kind of bad getting paid for something that felt that good.
Well, stop that.
Just don't get serious about me and we're fine.
Oh, so this is kind of a reverse prostitution thing.
I guess that's okay.
Right?
Don't mind me, just delivering your mail.
Oh, thank you.
To Lord Rudeus Greyrat, I hope this letter finds you well.
I am Genus Vice-Principal of the Rinoa University of Magic.
Wait a sec, holy crap!
That's Roxy's alma mater!
Word of your exploits is Quagmire Rudeus has reached us here in the Kingdom of Rinoa.
I understand you can cast spells without incantations,
and I've been informed that you also studied under Roxy Magurdia, a King-class Water Mage.
Should you have any desire to hone your magnificent craft further still,
Rinoa University of Magic would be honored to welcome you as a special student.
Ooh!
Sounds important.
Special students are exempt from both tuition and regular class attendance,
but retain full access to our on-campus libraries and other facilities
to conduct their own research as they see fit.
Wow!
Sounds like a good deal.
Would love to meet with you.
Thank you for your time and consideration.
Signed God knows who from God knows where.
I am glad someone appreciates my two years of hard work,
and it's true that my magic's kind of plateaued, so I am interested.
But I need to verify the authenticity of this thing.
Thank you for waiting.
Oh, that special student program. Good stuff.
So you do know it.
Yeah, I thought I'd heard that you attended school there.
Can you tell me anything more about it?
Well, I didn't graduate.
I dropped out in my fifth year.
But yeah, the university will sometimes reach out to people like you,
who can cast weird spells or have tons of mana,
but aren't associated with the Magician's Guild yet.
Then if they get famous later, that's good publicity for the school.
Okay, I guess that tracks.
I do cast weird spells.
And if they do this a lot, then it's probably not a total scam.
Wait, so you're telling me you've never been to school, Quagmire?
I had a private tutor.
Wow.
Your family must have been well off, then.
Sort of.
We have ties to Asura and High Nobility.
Right.
Sorry, remind me of your last name again?
Greyrat of the Notos Greyrats.
Oh.
Greyrat, huh?
The liege lords of Asura?
What are you doing as a solo adventurer way out here, then?
Well, my folks...
Oh, uh...
I shouldn't have asked.
But they went out of their way to offer you a pretty good deal.
You might as well go down there and hear them out at least.
You know?
Yeah.
And come to think of it, the only reason I went to Tudor Eris in the first place was so I could save up tuition money.
I'd totally forgotten.
Attending the university with Sylphie was the original goal.
I wonder what she's been up to all this time.
I hope she's alright.
You should listen to him.
School is a wonderful option.
Especially when the only alternative would be rejoining Paul.
You think?
I feel like reuniting my family ought to come first.
Paul is eventually going to bring them all back to Asura anyway.
Just wait till they make it back safely and get settled in and then take a shorter trip to visit them.
You're saying that because you don't want to see my father again, aren't you?
Guilty as charged.
Whoa, she must really hate him.
Well, improving my skills is important.
But attractive as the university's proposal is, I don't think I can justify taking them up on it right now.
Long time no see.
Yep, hi.
What has it been, two years now?
I don't feel as nasty as I did before.
Aw, you missed me, huh?
That's not what I said.
Although, hey, I did try to reach out to you a bunch of times while I was out looking for Zenith.
Would it have killed you to show up for me even once?
I had a lot going on on my end.
Aw, yeah.
Well, at least someone eventually found her.
Just feels like I lost two whole years over it.
Yeah, sorry.
But I'm glad you know where she is.
Thanks.
I had no idea Roxy was out there looking for her, too.
She's a real go-getter, isn't she?
Yeah, you said it.
But I hope she gets back from Beggarite sooner than later.
I can't wait to see her.
Oh, dear.
Are you sure you want your master to see how pathetic you are right now?
Hey.
I mean, think about it.
Aeris ran out on you.
And when you finally had a good thing going with Sarah, your little guy just wouldn't go to bat for you.
Your spellcasting may have improved a little, but you're really hitting a wall lately.
And your swordsmanship hasn't gotten any better either.
I know you practice every day, but boy, you don't have much to show for it.
Sure, you've built some muscle, but I don't think you can stand before her and say with any confidence that you're a student to be proud of, Rudy.
Wow, you're really letting me have it this time, huh?
How about you get to the point already?
The point is that you have a chance to shape up!
Attend the university, and I can promise you this.
You'll learn so much more than a common adventurer could ever hope to.
What are you?
Every teacher I had in high school?
Oh, wait.
You just kind of threw that out there, but is that more of your patented godly advice?
Sure, you could say that.
You do this thing where literally everything you say sounds suspicious and creepy.
Sorry!
But you really should listen this time.
I'm giving it to you as straight as I can.
If you set out for Beggarite now, you will most assuredly regret it.
Really? Why?
Can't tell you.
Of course you can't.
Well, this isn't the first time you've kept something important from me,
but you've got to realize that this whole interdimensional man of mystery thing
doesn't exactly make a strong argument for whatever you're trying to get me to do.
I'd love to take time for myself, but I'd much rather find the rest of my family first.
I see.
Well, why don't I put it to you another way?
This ought to be good.
Rudeus, enroll in the Rinoa University of Magic
and investigate the displacement incident with their abundant resources.
If you do, you shall once again regain your manly potency
and, more importantly, your pride!
Huh? Really?
Are you saying that just by going to school, I can cure my erectile dysfunction?
You are right!
Sure enough, not a peep from the peen.
Well, okay.
Guess it'll get better.
Thank you for everything.
Good luck, kid.
Take care of yourself.
Sol, I really appreciate you.
Huh?
I don't know how I can ever repay all the things that you and your party have done for me.
He may not want to admit it, but he's taken really good care of me these past couple of years.
In fact, I've made pretty nice money exploiting your ass, so thanks for that.
Anyway, safe travels.
Go get cured.
Yeah, I'll try.
Good.
Well, I'm sure we'll have business over in Rinoa one of these days.
And when that happens, we ought to go drinking and whoring again, just the two of us.
And so, I set out for the kingdom of Rinoa.
And so, I'm going to go to the kingdom of Rinoa.
Laya, Laya